Guide to the Records of the Barbara Goldsmith Preservation and Conservation Department RG.38.24
New York University Archives
- Series XII: Association of Research Libraries (ARL)
  - ARL Preservation Statistics, 1996-1997 (Box 11, Folder 21)
- Series XII: Conservation Documentation
  - Subseries A: Conservation Logbooks
    - Conservation Logbook, 2004 (Box 12, Folder 1)
    - Conservation Logbook, 2005 (Box 12, Folder 2)
    - Conservation Logbook, 2006 (Box 12, Folder 3)
    - Conservation Logbook, 2007 (Box 12, Folder 4)
    - Conservation Logbook, 2008 (Box 12, Folder 5)
    - Conservation Logbook, 2009 (Box 12, Folder 6)
  - Subseries B: Conservation Documentation
    - Conservation Documentation No. 04-001 - 04-020, 2004 (Box 12, Folder 7)
    - Conservation Documentation No. 05-001 - 05-100, 2004 (Box 12, Folder 8)
    - Conservation Documentation No. 05-101 - 05-450, 2005 (Box 12, Folder 9)
    - Conservation Documentation No. 06-001 - 06-050, 2006 (Box 12, Folder 10)
    - Conservation Documentation No. 06-051 - 06-102, 2006-2007 (Box 12, Folder 11)
    - Conservation Documentation No. 07-001 - 07-052, 2007 (Box 12, Folder 12)
    - Conservation Documentation No. 07-053 - 07-084, 2007 (Box 12, Folder 13)
    - Conservation Documentation No. 07-085 - 07-096, 2007 (Box 12, Folder 14)
    - Conservation Documentation No. 08-001 - 08-046, 2008 (Box 12, Folder 15)
    - Conservation Documentation No. 08-047 - 08-0100, 2008 (Box 12, Folder 16)
    - Conservation Documentation No. 08-101 - 08-0148, 2008 (Box 12, Folder 17)
    - Conservation Documentation No. 09-001 - 09-039, 2009 (Box 12, Folder 18)
    - Conservation Documentation No. 09-040 - 09-075, 2009 (Box 12, Folder 19)
    - Conservation Documentation No. 09-076 - 09-100, 2009 (Box 12, Folder 20)
    - Conservation Documentation No. 09-101 - 09-140, 2009 (Box 12, Folder 21)
    - Conservation Documentation No. 09-141 - 09-170, 2009 (Box 12, Folder 22)
    - Conservation Documentation No. 09-171 - 09-189, 2009 (Box 12, Folder 23)
    - Conservation Documentation No. 09-191 - 09-200, 2009 (Box 12, Folder 24)
    - Conservation Documentation No. 09-201 - 09-220, 2009 (Box 12, Folder 25)